This programme contains
some violent scenes
and some strong language.
BABY CRIES IN DISTANCE
GUNSHOT
DOG BARKS
KNOCKING AT DOOR
HE BLOWS A RASPBERRY
RINGING
HE WEEPS
PHONE RINGS
TYRES SCREECH
TELEPHONE RINGS
PHONE RINGS
ENGAGED TONE
KNOCKING
ANIMATED VOICES
RAISED VOICES
PHONE RINGS
INAUDIBLE
KNOCKING
DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES >
HE DIALS OUT
KNOCKING ON DOOR
GUNSHOTS
TYRES SCREECH
PHONE RINGS
Argh!
ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS OVER SCENE
# Met you by surprise
MUSIC OVER AUDIO:
# I didn't realise
# That my life would change
# For ever
# Saw you standing there
# I didn't know or care
# There was something special
# In the air
# Dreams are my reality
# The only kind of real fantasy. #
MUSIC STOPS ABRUPTLY
KNOCKING ON DOOR
NO SPEECH
BELL TOLLS
PHONE RINGING
SCREECHES TO HALT
THEY CHEER
Livia!
MUSIC: Lu Jorno Ca Cantavanu Li Manu
sung by Olivia Sellerio
KNOCKING AT DOOR
HE COUGHS VIOLENTLY
GUNSHOT
No, no!
PHONE RINGS
KNOCK AT DOOR
CHICKENS CLUCK
KNOCKING AT DOOR